<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Games on Geekosaur</title>
    <link>https://geekosaur.com/tags/games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Games on Geekosaur</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 16:32:19 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://geekosaur.com/tags/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Finished Control Game</title>
      <link>https://geekosaur.com/post/finished-control-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 16:32:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekosaur.com/post/finished-control-game/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After so many months without playing it, and then some time trying to beat it, I finally completed Control&amp;rsquo;s main story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A couple weeks ago I got stuck in the last battle, and after dying many times I stopped playing it for a while. A bit because of the frustration, but also because I got Fall Guys on PS4, and a Nintendo Switch with Animal Crossing and Streets of Rage 4. Then this week I decided to give it another try, and was pleasantly surprised with an update that added assist options.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Old AMVs</title>
      <link>https://geekosaur.com/post/good-old-amvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 14:08:36 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekosaur.com/post/good-old-amvs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I remember many years ago (like, 2 decades) when I used to go to anime conventions and actually watch anime and AMVs. The 2000s were when the otaku culture was still beginning in Brazil, and internet and subbed anime was not common at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes I remember a few AMVs that I used to watch from time to time, and get a really nostalgic feeling. I still have a CD with AMVs somewhere, all of them downloaded on Kazaa. Maybe one day I&amp;rsquo;ll find it and see what other videos it contains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, below I have a few AMVs from my early otaku days, 3 from anime, and 2 from games. Hope you enjoy! And leave a comment on the linked reddit post below, with your favorite AMVs ever!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My PS4 Games List</title>
      <link>https://geekosaur.com/post/my-ps4-games-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 18:28:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekosaur.com/post/my-ps4-games-list/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago, Notion.so was made free for personal use. One of the things I decided to use it to, is to organize my game&amp;rsquo;s list, mainly PS4. Not that I have a lot, but it&amp;rsquo;s still cool to plan what I&amp;rsquo;m going to play next.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>